spinlet.com 2010-06-06

# Free iPhone Application, An online Social Music Network, Spinlet

This statement applies to Spinlet(TM) services, mobile offering and website (“services”). 

## Scope

Spinlet collects information when you register for a Spinlet service or otherwise voluntarily provide such information. We may combine personal information collected from you with information from other Spinlet services or third parties to provide a better user experience, including customizing content for you. 

Spinlet may use cookies and other technologies to enhance your experience and to learn about how you use Spinlet services in order to improve the quality of our services. Spinlet’s servers may automatically record information when you visit our website or use some of our products, including the URL, IP address, and the date and time of your request. 

## Uses

We may use personal information to provide the services you’ve requested, such as content delivery, content transport, content storage, content profiling etc. 

We may use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve Spinlet services and related products. We may also share information with third parties including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services. 

Spinlet processes personal information on our servers in the European Union, United States of America and in other countries. In some cases, we process personal information on a server outside your country. 

## Your Choices

We offer you choices when we ask for personal information, whenever reasonably possible. You may decline to provide personal information to us and/or refuse cookies in your browser, although our features or services may not function properly as a result. We make good faith efforts to provide you access to your personal information upon request and to let you correct such data if it is inaccurate and delete it, when reasonably possible. 

## Other

We may amend privacy information in Spinlet services. Such information prevails over this Policy to the extent of any conflict. By using this website and/or by submitting personal data to Spinlet, you express your agreement to the processing of your personal data in the manner provided in this Policy. If you do not agree with this Policy, please do not use this mobile service or website or provide Spinlet with your personal data.   

We collect your personal data typically when you submit information into our services or otherwise interact with us. Certain technical information is normally collected as a standard part of your use of our services. Such information includes, for example, your IP-address, access times, the website you linked from, pages you visit, the links you use, the adbanners and other content you viewed, information about your devices and other such technical information your browser provides us with or as may be otherwise collected in connection with certain products and services. When you use our services or otherwise interact with us over telecommunications networks, certain additional information, such as your mobile subscription number, may be transmitted to us by the telecommunications operator as a standard part of that communication. Please also see the section “Use of Cookies and Web Beacons” below. 

Information you provide us with When you register for our services, we may ask you to provide us with information such as your name, email address, street address, as well as user names, passwords and other such credentials that are used to authenticate users and to validate their actions or that may be needed to provide you with the products and services you have requested or to communicate with you. 

We may collect demographic information, for example, your age, gender, postal code and language preferences. We may also collect other information you provide, such as your consents, preferences and feedback, information relating to your devices and other such information you provide us with. Please note that certain non-identifiable information collected from you may become personally identifiable when you provide us with your personal data. We may also obtain, in accordance with applicable law, some personal data from list-rental companies and other such publicly available sources. Some of our services may allow you to submit information about other people, for example, if you make an order for a product that you wish us to send directly to another recipient. Certain spinlet services may involve the use of your location dataand/or media consumption data. 

## Development of products and services

We may use your personal data to develop our products and/or services. However, for the most part we only use aggregate and statistical information in the development of our products and services. We may also use your personal data to personalize our offering and to provide you with service more relevant to you, for example, to make recommendations and to display customized content and advertising in our websites. We may combine personal data collected in connection with your use of a particular Spinlet product and/or service with other personal data we may hold about you, except where such personal data was collected for a different purpose. We may create aggregate and statistical information based on your personal data. 

## Communicating with you and marketing

We may use your personal data to communicate with you, for example, to provide information relating to our products and/or services you are using or to contact you for customer satisfaction queries. We may use your personal data for marketing or research purposes, for example, to conduct market research and we may, in accordance with applicable law, contact you to inform you of new products, services or promotions we may offer. Also, some of our products and services may be used to promote products and services of other companies. However, Spinlet does not disclose your personal data to such companies or any other company for marketing purposes without your prior consent. 

Some services may include sharing your personal data with other users of the service, for example services where users publish their content with Spinlet mobile services. 

## Mergers and Acquisitions

If we decide to sell, buy, merge or otherwise reorganise our businesses, this may involve us disclosing personal data to prospective or actual purchasers and their advisers, or receiving personal data from sellers and their advisers. Spinlet’s policy is to request that minors (the legal age of majority and therefore the age of minors is determined by local law where you reside) do not make content submissions or engage in any legal acts on our products and services without the consent of a parent or legal guardian, unless otherwise permitted by applicable law. 

There are always risks associated with providing personal data, whether in person, by phone, via the internet or otherwise, and no technology is completely safe, Spinlet takes appropriate technical and organizational information security measures to prevent and minimize such risks. Such measures include, where appropriate, the use of industry standard security measure, such as the one available through “Secure Sockets Layer” (“SSL”), to protect the confidentiality and security of online transactions. 

Please note that Spinlet may need to identify you and to ask for additional information in order to be able to fulfill your above request. Please also note that applicable law may contain restrictions and other provisions that relate to your above rights. 

## The Controller of Your Personal Data and Contact Details

Spinlet Ltd.  
It. Rantakatu 60a  
FIN-20810 Turku Finland EU  

In addition, the Spinlet affiliate providing the product or service may be a controller of your personal data. You may find the identity of the controller and its contact details by reviewing the terms and conditions of such a product or service or by using contact information provided in the applicable Spinlet websites. 

In matters pertaining to Spinlet’s privacy practices you may also contact us at:  
Spinlet Ltd.  
info@spinlet.com  

Spinlet may from time to time change this Privacy Policy or change, modify or withdraw access to this site at any time with or without notice.
